<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>KPIT Digital Thought Leadership Series</title>
    <description>Exclusive Series by KPIT, published on Forbes India website, on how Digital and Engineering are Transforming the World</description>
    <link>https://www.kpit.com/articles/kpit-digital-thought-leadership-series-in-forbesindia</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 00:01:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 June 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate>

    <ttl>1800</ttl>
	
	<item>
<title>
Machine-to-Machine: Manufacturing in a connected world
</title>
<description>
In this constantly connected world, businesses are increasingly turning to machine-to-machine communications (M2M) and analytics as clean data is becoming a pre-requisite for companies to optimise productivity
</description>
<link>
https://www.kpit.com/articles/machine-to-machine-manufacturing-in-a-connected-world
</link>
<pubDate>Tue, 25, Sep 2018 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
	
	
	
	
	
	
	
		<item>
<title>
Smart Transportation: A Key Building Block for a Smart City
</title>
<description>
By creating a connected ecosystem wherein people execute their journeys seamlessly, smart transportation can improve the way people use their time and enhance the quality of their lives-in the cities of today and tomorrow.
</description>
<link>
https://www.kpit.com/articles/smart-transportation-the-key-building-block-for-a-smart-city
</link>
<pubDate>Fri, 6, July 2018 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
	
	
	
	<item>
<title>
The business value of enabling IoT in industrial manufacturing
</title>
<description>
As digital disruption paves the way for the entry of agile, tech-driven startups, it is incentivising big, established manufacturing companies to rewire their business models
</description>
<link>
https://www.kpit.com/articles/enabling-iot-in-industrial-manufacturing
</link>
<pubDate>Mon, 11, June 2018 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>	
	
	
	
	
	
	
	
<item>
<title>
Erasing boundaries for a unique customer experience
</title>
<description>
The coming together of digital technologies, such as big data, connected assets, cloud, mobility and predictive modelling can create and enable such a boundaryless exchange.
</description>
<link>
https://www.kpit.com/articles/erasing-boundaries-for-a-unique-customer-experience
</link>
<pubDate>Wed, 16, May 2018 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>	
<item>
<title>
The role of autonomous driving technology in India
</title>
<description>
Fully self-driving cars use the latest technology within an entire spectrum of autonomous technologies, and the latest technology is not always the most appropriate for a society.
</description>
<link>
https://www.kpit.com/articles/the-role-of-autonomous-driving-technology-in-india
</link>
<pubDate>Thu, 21, Apr 2018 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
	</item>
	
<item>
<title>
Electric buses: An opportunity to transform public transport in India
</title>
<description>
Electric vehicles and buses are a great way to curb India's pollution problem. But what will make Indians ditch their cars and use the public transportation system for maximum effect?
</description>
<link>
https://www.kpit.com/articles/electric-buses-an-opportunity-to-transform-public-transport-in-india
</link>
<pubDate>Wed, 14, Feb 2018 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
	<item>
<title>
How smart glasses are transforming backend processes in manufacturing
</title>
<description>
Within warehouses, order-picking accounts for an estimated 55 percent of the total warehouse operating expenses. Underperformance in this task negatively affects the cost and performance of a warehouse.
</description>
<link>
http://www.kpit.com/articles/how-smart-glasses-are-transforming
</link>
<pubDate>Sat, 18, Nov 2017 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
	<item>
<title>
Automated fuel stations: Enhancing customer experience using analytics at retail points
</title>
<description>
From being just a place for a need-based, 'distress purchase' of fuel, automated fuel stations can be the integration point for a range of services.
</description>
<link>
https://www.kpit.com/articles/automated-fuel-stations-enhancing-customer-experience-using-analytics-at-retail-points
</link>
<pubDate>Tue, 3 Oct 2017 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>
Disruptions in the global automotive industry: Solutions from India?
</title>
<description>
India's challenges require scale to be a part of the solution so logically, any product designed for India's scale would be in a better position to be adopted by the rest of the world, than the other way around.
</description>
<link>
https://www.kpit.com/articles/disruptions-in-the-global-automotive-industry-solutions-from-india
</link>
<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
    
<item>
      <title>Supply chain optimisation using technology in manufacturing</title>
      <description>Technology-enabled processes are providing manufacturers a bird's eye view of the entire supply line. This comes with its benefits and challenges.</description>
      <link>https://www.kpit.com/articles/supply-chain-optimisation-using-technology-in-manufacturing</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart Cities-India's next tech opportunity to lead the world</title>
      <description>With its talented manpower and IT prowess, India can show the world how mass-scale, flexible and affordable smart city infrastructure can be created and replicated anywhere across the globe.</description>
      <link>https://www.kpit.com/articles/smart-cities-indias-next-tech-opportunity-to-lead-the-world</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making connected factories a reality in India</title>
      <description>A shift that is aligning with where the manufacturing industry the world over is heading-towards a more interconnected, agile and flexible production process to seemingly fuse man, technology and machine.</description>
      <link>https://www.kpit.com/articles/making-connected-factories-a-reality-in-india</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2017 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
